>> Jem Young: 第 1 部，这就是我的封面，有点这个。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Parts 1s, this is where I
cover bit of this, a little bit of that.
我认为你应该拥有的一般知识
Just general knowledge that
I think you should have.
但今天运行您的应用程序并不一定是核心。
But it's not necessarily core to
running your application today.
我想说的第一件事就是标准流
The first thing I wanna talk
about it standard streams.
有人知道标准和标准是什么，这听起来很熟悉吗 ?
Anybody know what standard in and standard
out, does that sound familiar to anybody?
是啊你可能已经习惯了
Yeah, you've probably used it.
如果你写了任何 Unix 或
If you've written any sort of Unix or
即使是一个音符应用程序也要用这些东西
even a note application
you use these things too.
有些东西叫做标准流
There's things called standard streams,
标准输出就是标准输出你会看到它写的
they're standard output which is stdout
that you'll see it written as that.
标准输入标准输入，标准错误，标准错误。
Standard input stdin, and
there's standard error, stderr.
这很棒，因为这是几乎所有 Unix 应用程序的标准。
It's great because this is the standard
for almost all Unix applications.
有个叫 POSIX 标准的东西
There's something called
the POSIX standards, which,
我不记得 POSIX 是什么意思，但它在音符中。
I don't remember what POSIX means,
but it's in the notes.
便携式操作系统接口。
Portable Operating System Interface.
所以它是一群人决定了，嘿，如果你在写任何一种 Unix
So it's a group of people that decided,
hey, if you're writing any sort of Unix
应用程序，应该有某种标准的输入输出或
application, there should be some sort
of standard way that inputs come out or
输入输入，输出超时并处理错误。
inputs go in, outputs go out and
errors are handled.
你已经在电话里看到过如果你写了任何
And you've already seen in call backs
everywhere if you've written any sort of
节点应用程序，您会看到它总是发送给它，发送出去，发送到错误或
node application, you'll see it's always
send it in, send it out, send to error or
那些线条里的东西
something along those lines.
这真是太棒了它突出了我们昨天说的
And it is really awesome cuz it highlights
what we're talking about yesterday how
互联网是建立在信任之上的
the Internet is build on trust.
信任与合作是惊人的。
And trust and
cooperation which is amazing.
尤其是在当今世界，我们都不同意什么是最棒的。
Especially in today's world where we all
disagree about what is the best burritos.
在世界上最适合居住的地方是这样的。
And where's the best place to live
in the world, things like that.
但你知道我们都同意一切都应该有标准
But you know what we all agree that
everything should have standard out,
标准误差和标准误差。
standard in and standard error.
它让程序真的很容易阅读。
And it makes programs really,
really readable.
这意味着任何一个我正在运行的 Unix 程序，我可以管输入，
That means any sort of Unix program
that I'm running, I can pipe the input,
我可以管输出，我可以把错误管到标准的地方。
I can pipe the output,
I can pipe the errors to a standard place.
他们都处理好了我知道
And they're all handled and
I know that for
他们都能分享这个共同的API
a fact it's gonna work cuz they
all share this common API.
我们用这些输入，输出和
And what we do with these inputs,
outputs, and
错误是使用被调用的重定向。
errors is we use something
called redirection.
你昨天看到我用管工的时候
You saw yesterday when I
use the pipe operator.
所以管道运营商就是从标准出来的一个很好的例子，
So the pipe operator is a good
example of reading from standard out,
因为我做了什么然后所有的输出都给我管了
because I run something and then all
the output I pipe it to something else.
让我们举个例子。
Let's do an example of that.
如果您尚未登录，请转至您的服务器，然后让我清除此问题。
Just go and log in to your server if
you're not already on, let me clear this.
>> Jem Young: 我想跑什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And what do I wanna run?
我说， ps，什么都没发生。
I'll say, ps, nothing happening.
Ps 正给我展示我的跑步过程
Ps is just showing me
my running processes.
但如果我想把这个写在档案里我可以说
But if I wanna write this to a file,
I can say ps.
其实我也会去查的
And actually I'll do a search for it.
然后我就会去找你了然后我就会说巴什
And then I'll do grep to do a search,
and I'll say bash.
就这样了 所以它把所有的输出都拿走了
That was it.
So it took all the output from ps, and
然后就把它写在 grep program上了。
then it just wrote it
over to the grep program.
然后格雷普会对它做一个普通的正则表达式。
And then grep is gonna do a general
regular expression on it.
然后它只搜索我想要的一切并返回线路。
And then it just searches over
everything I want and returns the line.
这是重定向运算符。
That's a redirection operator.
所以我们可以用重定向做很多事情。
So we could do lots of
things with redirection.
我们可以编写文件，可以从文件中读取。
We can write the files,
we can read from files.
我可以做一些非常复杂的事情，你喜欢的不是真正的代码。
I can do some really complex things
that you're like that's not real code.
这一点都没道理
This doesn't make any sense.
但我可以
But it does, I can.
但我决定离开这些例子因为他们看起来很酷
But I decided to leave out those examples
because they're just cool looking and
他们其实也不知道
they don't actually do.
白天他们不会帮你所以我今天不想走那条路
They won't help you in your day to day, so
I don't wanna go down that route today.
你见过的另一个是错误运算符
Another one you've seen
is the error operator or
大于运算符或箭头 ( 如果您愿意的话 ) 。
the greater than operator,
or that arrow if you will.
它将写入文件。
It will write to a file.
所以不要把它从一边打字
So rather than typing it
from one side to the other,
只要你愿意就能把它写在档案里
it's just gonna write to the file,
if you want.
这对于写入日志文件非常有用。
This is super useful for
writing to a log file.
因此，我将创建一个假日志文件。
So I'll create a fake log file.
所以我会说点什么
So I'll say touch.
实际上，让我确定我在我的主目录里。
Actually, let me make sure
that I'm in my home directory.
把它关了
Close that out.
我要说的是 CD 和清晰的
I'll say CD and clear.
我说 PS 其实
And I'll say PS- Actually,
请允许我清除锁定，触摸 test.log。
let me clear locks out, touch test.log.
我说 PS 我去写 test.log
I'll say PS and I'll write to test.log.
什么都没发生因为输出被写在了
And nothing happened because the output
was being gobbled up by writing to this
日志文件。
log file.
但如果我们保存了日志文件，我们发现它只写了所有输出。
But if we kept the log file,
we see that it just wrote all that output.
现在很多时候你要做的就是输出
Now a lot of times what you're gonna
do is you're gonna take output and
你会把它写在档案里
you're gonna write it to log files.
最伟大的是，您输入所有常用的日志文件。
And what's great about that is you type
all the log files that are commonplace.
您是否记得通常保存日志文件的位置 ?
Do you remember where the log
files are kept generally?
没人响铃吗
Nobody ringing a bell?
没事的没事的
It's okay.
斜杠 " 斜杠 " 日志是您始终保留所有
Slash bar slash log is the economical
place where you always keep all of
您的日志。
your logs.
所以我们可以说
So we can say,
实际上让我们来看看我们的日志，因为我们在一段时间内没有看到过这个。
actually let's take at our log since
we haven't looked at that in a while.
>> Jem Young: 您将看到所有日志
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: You see all the logs for
你的所有服务总是写在同一个地方
all your services are always gonna
be written in the same place.
所以，一般来说，如果你在做任何记录，你总是想把它放在这里。
So generally if you're doing any sort
of logging you always want put it here.
你看到有一个引擎的 x 日志，上面有一个日志。
So you see there's an engine x log,
there's off the log.
让我看看我能不能
Let me see if I can sudo ls and
/var/log。
/var/log.
是啊它什么都没给我看
Yeah, it didn't show me anything new.
但输出的文字可能是比较常见的
But the writing to output is probably
one of the more common ones, and
还有一个管道
also the piping one.
如果你见过那些擅长 Unix 的人
If you've ever seen people who
are good at their Unix fu,
你会发现他们从 AWK 和他们的废话中就会把事情链过去
you'll see they just chain things over and
over as they go from AWK and their crap.
他们可以运行 Perl 脚本在命令行上做些神奇的事情
They might run a Perl script and they'll
do just amazing things on the command line
使用重定向运算符，因为我们知道有一个标准
using the redirection operator, all
because we know that there's a standard
in， standard out和 standard 错误。
in, standard out, and standard error.
我很喜欢这个，因为它展示了一个普通的 API的力量。
And I really love this because it shows
the power of just having a common API.
当你有这个完善的模式时，你可以做这些神奇的事情。
And when you have this well established
pattern, you can do such amazing things.
现在如果你想把问题写在一个标准的档案里
Now if you wanna just, the problems
writing to a standard out file,
它会把你以前的一切都搞砸了
it's gonna blow away
whatever you had before.
所以如果你想参加它，你只会做翻倍，大于，看。
So if you want to attend it,
you just do the double, greater than, see.
是啊我有个笑话
Yeah, I got I got a chuckle.
谢谢你 Zach
Thank you, Zach.
我很感激
I appreciate that.
如果你想从星期六开始读我们就用另一种方式
If you want to read from Saturday and
we just type it the other way.
因此，我们可以将文件输入到我们正在尝试运行的程序中。
So we can take a file and type it into
the the program that we're trying to run.
标准误差有点不同，两者都比。
And standard error is a little different,
it's the two with greater than.
这有点奇怪但我觉得他们真的是从符号中跑出来的
It's a little weird, but
I think they ran out of symbols honestly.
我想这就是为什么它是两个
I think that's why it's a two.
很奇怪的事实你可能看到了
Weird useless fact, but you might see it.
如果我想写一个标准，其实是一个大的。
If I wanna write a standard out,
it's actually a one greater than.
如果我想从标准中读到，它实际上是一个零。
And if I wanna read from standard in,
it's actually a zero less than.
但我没放进去，卡兹你不会经常看到那种格式。
But I didn't put that in there,
cuz you won't see that format that often.
但如果你是这样的话我真的很喜欢洗劫
But in case you're like, man, I really
love full sack I want to look things up.
您可能会在某处看到该语法，并且
You might see that syntax somewhere, and
那么这两个大于标准误差。
then the two greater
than the standard error.
所以实际上是 0， 1和 2。
So it's actually 0, 1, 2.
所以它的标准是标准的，标准的误差。
So its standard in,
standard out, standard error.
现在，你看到两个大的感觉就更有意义了吗 ?
Makes a little more sense now now
you see the two greater than?
是吗 ?
Yeah?
好吧好吧
All right.
有些头我知道它早我就直接跳下去了
Some heads, I know it's early and
I just jumped right in.
别担心我要从这里开始慢慢地下去
Don't worry, I'm gonna start off here and
we're gonna slowly ramp down and
然后我要向你撒谎然后我们要回去了
then I'm gonna lie to you, and
then we're gonna ramp back up and
那将是一个伟大的日子
then it's gonna be a great day.
好吧这到底是干什么的
All right, so what does this do?
只是为了向任何人展示任何一个人吗
Just to show the anybody, anybody at all?
什么事萨姆
Yes, Sam?
> > Sam: 接受 foo 并将其写入条形图。
&gt;&gt; Sam: Takes foo and it writes it to bar.
>> Jem Young: 完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Exactly.
你会经常看到这个的
You'll see this quite often though, so
稍后在这个过程中可能就会做这样的事情。
later in the course will
probably do something like this.
我想让你熟悉语法
And I want you to be
familiar with the syntax.
但如果你需要参考的话这很直接
But if you ever need to reference,
this is pretty straightforward, hopefully